Homer Leroy Shantz papers, 1903-1958
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Home Notes on 1949 and Previous Field Notes. 1949 (Box 33, Folder 201)
- Photos; Soil Temperatures. 1949 (Box 33, Folder 202)
- Navajo Report. March 1951 (Box 33, Folder 203)
- Navajo Report. October 1951 (Box 33, Folder 204)
- Diary. 1952 (Box 33, Folder 205)
- Field Notes (Eastern Colorado; Utah). June-July 1953 (Box 33, Folder 206)
- Field Notes, Thoughts, Various Trips. 1955-1957 (Box 33, Folder 207)
- Diary and Field Notes (Africa). August-October 1956 (Box 33, Folder 208)
- Diary and Field Notes (Africa). October-December 1956-January-February 1957 (Box 33, Folder 209)
- Diary and Field Notes (Africa). February-April 1957 (Box 33, Folder 210)
- Notes on Reading, Meetings, Ecology 66 at the University of Arizona. 1955 (Box 34, Folder 211)
- Additional Notes on Africa. List of Specimens Given to the University of Arizona, Arizona State Museum. Notes on Reading Early Western Travels, Forests. 1919-1920?; 1943 (Box 34, Folder 212)
- This Books Contains Many Specimens Collected for Identification Only, i.e., plants which cannot be collected in flower or possiblly fruit, but which may possibly be identified in order to complete field notes. (Africa). 1919-1920 (Box 34, Folder 213)
- Retake Photos & Studies to Document Changes, 2CR-ONR-Africa. H.L. Shantz, Chief Investigator. B.L. Turner, Associate Investigator. (Box 34, Folder 214)
- Herbarium Collections, 2CR-ONR-Africa. University of Arizona, Department of Botony. H.L. Shantz, Chief Investigator. BlL. Turner, Associate Investigator. (Box 34, Folder 215)